Wow, wow, wow.
Android is an open source operating system, which is widely used in mobile devices, but it's also
used in automotive devices, elevations via devices, etc. It has also a corresponding open source project,
which is led by Google on the right side.
You can see a high level architecture diagram of areas.
So as you can see, Android has multiple layers at the bottom.
We can find Linux kernel, so Android is built on top of Linux kernel.
And about that there is the hull, which is the hardware abstraction layer and Ebo that we have the
Android runtime or the Dalvik virtual machine.
At the same level, we have the native libraries, which are mostly written in C and C++, and on top
we have the Android framework, which is written in Java and at the topmost we have the apps.
So as a normal Android user will be mostly interacting with the apps and the Android framework, and
the native libraries are basically a mediator between the apps and the hull or the next.
So we'll discuss in detail about each of this layer in a later section.
Next, I would like to introduce you to source code Android dot com.
So Asana is platform developer.
You should definitely look at this website.
You get a lot of information about areas.
You can find the English version here.
So a certain protocol, if you need any submission, you could use this one.
There is also a link to the code provided by Google.
So if you click on, this will take you to the the code and here you can see the branch.
It is the master now.
So if you want to quickly reference rather the code of Areas area be, then you can use this link.
See usto Android.
And here you can search for whatever modules you want and similar to an editor.
You can use these, but only for reading purpose.
A search for system.
You're here, then you can see the module and system.
You are related classes here and here.
You have the option to change the branch.
So if you are looking for some other branch, you can, of course, is that branch is here.
And if you are looking for some commits that also you can see here in source code Android dot com,
you can find a lot of information about areas under the docks.
You can see different documentations for getting started.
Security core topics, compatibility, Android devices, preference Android getting started There is
very good information about how to download and build a new project.
Here, you can find information about the platform structure, development, environment, setup, downloading
and building the source customizations, and some information on how to contribute to Android open source
project.
Under security, you can get an overview of Android security at different levels, like in an Android
application or even in the Canon 11.
It also details the security features provided by Android like sea, Linux, Keystone encryption, authentication
and app signing.
There is information on how to perform security test on your airways, be built and some best practices
for security under court topics.
You can find a lot of information on different building blocks of Android.
That is a detailed explanation about the architecture and many essential modules in Android like audio,
camera, media, etc...
Under compatibility, you can find the compatibility definition document and compatibility test related
information.
These are important if you plan to build a pure Android device.
If you want to keep Android local on your device, you should pass these seats tests or compatibility
test tube tests.
You run the city's test for your AOSP build and send it to Google for approval.
But this is not mandatory.
If you're simply building a device that does not need Android logo, then this is optional.
These tests are quality gates to ensure that your build meets a basic quality standards set by Google
under the Android devices.
We can find information specific to automotive, enterprise and TV.
And finally, there is a reference section under which you find more information about the Hull Hardware
Abstraction Layer, its radial hull interface, definition, language and trade federation, which is
basically a testing framework for continuous testing.
Wow.
Wow, wow.